CHRISTIAN BROWN

UX/UI DESIGNER

UX/UI designer with a background in hospitality management, specifically restaurant and customer service environments. Experience in customer and employee relations and problem solving daily operational issues. Skilled in optimizing employee workflow and customer satisfaction using design practices, with a passion for collaboration and strong work moral.

New York, NY

+1 646-866-0306

christianbrown988@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/ christian-brown-4533a11b9/

Bē www.behance.net/christianbrown20

EDUCATION

Front-End Engineer

2023-Present | Codecademy

115 hour course using HTML, CSS, Javascript, React and more to develop clean code for interactive websites.

User Interface Design

2022 | Careerfoundry

500+ hours of UX/UI study. Research methods, visual elements and structure.

Popular Music & Recording Degree

2010 | Salford University, UK

1st class Honors Degree majoring in music technology and performance.

CAREER FOUNDRY PROJECTS

Elevate (Location based services)

Conducted UX practices to research competitors, created user personas and conducted usability testing. Drafted mood boards and implemented UI design for a responsive web app.

Maestro (Native iOS and Android)

Designed a musical instrument tutoring service app for both Android and iOS interfaces focusing on functionality and competitor research creating prototypes for user testing.

SKILLS

Branding/visual design Competitor analysis User personas User flow Wireframing
Prototyping
User testing
Usability analytics

TOOLS

Figma Sketch Adobe Creative Suite Adobe After Effects HTML5 & CSS

EXPERIENCE

Food & Beverage Manager

2023 - Present | Mermaid Oyster Bar | Times Square

- Achieved high levels of customer satisfaction which was reflected with positive online business reviews from effectively managing customer issues in the restaurant and event spaces.
- O Part of a leadership team braking record sales for the last quarter of 2023 hosting a range of events.
- Provided an important supporting role for the opening of a new restaurant within the company.

Restaurant Manager

2022 - 2023 | Saraghina Caffe | New York

- Improved bar functionality and streamlined the effectiveness of the liquor beer and wine program through a series of menu iterations.
- Trained new staff, performed inventory and supported the restaurant as a floor manager, maintaining customer satisfaction and general ambience.

Graphic Designer

2019 - 2022 | Grafted Cellars | California

- O Designed logos and corresponding brand aesthetic.
- Created a cohesive line of bottle label designs during a winery rebranding.
- O Created promotional graphics in Canva for winery events such as printed banners and newsletters.

Cellar Operations

2019 - 2022 | Grafted Cellars | California

- Collaborated with a small team to design a new storage system and organization techniques for inventory, which increased free space in wine cellar by 50% and allowed for additional wine bar seating and event use, generating a new revenue stream.
- Oversaw production and conducted time sensitive winemaking duties to an inventory of over 70 barrels and 5000 bottles.